What does self-discipline look like at work?
工作中的自律是什么样的？
Sometimes, it’s the ability to resist temptation, such as distractions to avoid a particular task.
有时，自律是抵制诱惑的能力，比如抵制那些分心的事，不借此逃避某项任务。
Other times it’s the ability to persist with a task when your energy and motivation seem low.
另一些时候，自律则是在你精力和动力似乎不足时，坚持把任务做下去的能力。
What do you believe about the nature of your own self-discipline?
你认为自己的自律本质上是怎样的？
Is it something that runs on internal energy that is spent with use?
它是不是靠内在能量运转，这种能量会随着使用而消耗掉？
Or is it something that is bolstered as you apply it and persist?
还是说，你运用它、坚持下去，它就会随之增强？
Your answer matters, as it determines how much self-discipline you experience.
你的答案很重要，因为它决定了你能体验到多少自律。
For years, research in psychology pointed to self-control as a resource that is depleted with use and needs to be restored through breaks, rest, or sleep.
多年来，心理学研究一直表明，自制力是一种会随着使用而耗竭的资源，需要通过中途休息、休整或睡眠来恢复。
More recently, however, research points to the importance of mindset.
然而，近来的研究则指出了心态的重要性。
If you view self-discipline as an expendable resource, your willpower tends to fade with use.
如果你把自律看作一种可消耗的资源，意志力往往就会越用越弱。
If you believe that exercising your self-control strengthens and fuels it, that is more likely to be your experience as you resist temptation or push yourself to get something done that is not appealing.
如果你相信运用自制力会增强它、为它提供动力，那么在你抵制诱惑或逼自己去完成某件并不吸引人的事时，你就更有可能有这样的体验。
If you don’t already view self-discipline as a force that feeds itself, what might you do?
如果你还没有把自律看作一种能自我滋养的力量，你可以怎么做呢？
Reflect on times that you had initial difficulty resisting temptation, getting started on something, or sticking with it, but pushed ahead and accomplished the task or met the goal.
回想一下那些时候：你起初很难抵制诱惑、很难着手做某件事或很难坚持做下去，但还是奋力向前，完成了任务或实现了目标。
That’s the kind of experience we’re talking about with this particular belief about self-discipline, and you’ve already had such an experience, so you’ve shown that it’s possible.
我们谈论对自律的这种特定看法时，说的就是这类经历；你已经有过这样的经历，也就证明了这是可能的。
When you feel your willpower and motivation fading, remind yourself of those previous experiences and imagine the same happening now.
感到意志力和动力逐渐减弱时，就提醒自己想想以前的那些经历，并想象同样的情形此刻正在发生。
What if your experiences have always seemed to indicate that your self-control diminishes with use, and you need breaks to recharge?
如果你的经历似乎一直表明，你的自制力会随着使用而减弱，你需要中途休息来恢复精力，那该怎么办？
There’s nothing wrong with that as long as you can afford to take those breaks.
只要你有条件这样中途休息，这就没什么不对。
If not, remind yourself that not everyone experiences self-discipline as a depletable resource and that your experience might be different if you focus on gathering more energy at this point rather than focusing on how difficult it is to continue or the need for a break.
如果没有这样的条件，就提醒自己：并非每个人都觉得自律是一种会耗尽的资源；而且，如果你此时专注于积聚更多精力，而不是一心想着继续下去有多难或自己需要休息，你的体验就可能会不同。
Also, if you know someone who is a role model of self-discipline, picture that person in your situation, persisting in the task.
此外，如果你认识某个在自律方面堪称榜样的人，就想象一下这个人身处你的境地、坚持做这项任务的情景。
Regardless of how you do it, as you push forward to continue to make progress, be sure to mentally reinforce yourself by taking pride in your ability to exert more willpower as you persist.
无论用什么方法，在你奋力向前、继续取得进展的过程中，一定要为自己在坚持中能运用更多意志力而感到自豪，以此在心理上强化自己。
The benefits of exerting willpower are cumulative.
运用意志力的好处会不断累积。
Your self-discipline is akin to a muscle, and each time you resist temptation or persist in a task despite a lack of motivation, you strengthen that muscle, leading to less effort and resistance in similar instances in the future.
你的自律就好比一块肌肉：每当你抵制诱惑，或者在缺乏动力的情况下依然坚持做一项任务，你都在让这块肌肉变得更强，从而使你今后在类似情况下需要付出的努力更少、内心的抗拒也更小。